ultrasurfing.com 2012-09-15

# Ultrasurf - Privacy Policy

**I. Scope of the Privacy Policy**

Ultrareach Internet Corporation and ultrasurfing.com (collectively, "Ultrareach," "we" or "our") understand the importance of our customers’ privacy. This Privacy Policy tells you what information we collect about you when you visit this website (our "Site") or use an online application that contains a link to this Privacy Policy. Our Privacy Policy also tells you how we use, share and protect this information; what choices you have about how this information is used; and how you can access and update this information. Our Site offers certain content, activities, and services, which are referred to as the "Services." This Privacy Policy applies to information collected on the Site where this Privacy Policy is posted. 

For purposes of this Privacy Policy, "personally identifiable information" means information that identifies and can be used to contact a particular individual, such as name, postal address, email address, and phone number. When other information, such as preferences, is associated with personally identifiable information, this other information also becomes personally identifiable information. 

**II. Information Collected**

Information You Provide Directly to Ultrareach:  
If you are interested in obtaining information, products or services from Ultrareach, or in participating in certain activities on this Site, you may elect to provide us with information about yourself. 

Information We Collect Automatically:  
In addition to information you choose to provide to us, we also use standard Internet technologies to collect automatically certain additional information. For example: IP Address. When you come to our Site, we may collect your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, which identifies the computer or service provider that you use to access the Site. We may use IP addresses to collect information regarding the frequency with which specific visitors visit various parts of our Site. If you have come to our Site through use of the Ultrasurf tool, your actual IP address will not be logged. 

Cookies:  
Our Site also uses cookies. Cookies are small text files that are stored on a user’s computer and allow websites to remember information about users. We use cookies for a variety of purposes in order to enhance the quality of our Site. We use transient (also called "session ID") cookies to provide continuity from page to page. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. We also use persistent cookies. Persistent cookies allow our Site to recognize your browser when you return after your first visit to that part of our Site. Cookies allow us to personalize your return visits to our Site and to save you time during certain activities. You have the choice to set your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) It is up to you whether to allow us to send you cookies. However, if you do not accept cookies from us, your ability to use some areas of our Site will be limited. If you have come to our site through use of the Ultrasurf tool, cookies will be erased when you close your session. 

Third-Party Online Advertising:  
Some of the advertisements you see on this Site and other websites are delivered by third parties who also collect information through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies about your online activities on this and other websites, in an effort to understand your interests and deliver to you advertisements that are tailored to your interests. These third parties also may use information about you to target and serve advertisements to you and to analyze the delivery of advertisements on the Site. However, we will not provide personally identifiable information about you to these companies, except as otherwise permitted under this Privacy Policy.

If you have come to our site using the Ultrasurf tool, personally identifying information such as your actual IP address or location will not be visible to any third parties. 

Third parties that currently serve ads on our Site, and thereby may collect information about your online activities to deliver tailored ads, may offer you a way to choose not to have your information used for advertising purposes. These and other third-party companies may also be members of the Network Advertising Initiative ("NAI"), which offers a single location to opt out of receiving tailored ads from member companies. To opt out or to obtain information about the technologies member companies use or their own privacy policies, please visit the NAI consumer opt out page. Also, through the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA"), several media and marketing associations have developed an industry self-regulatory program to give consumers a better understanding of and greater control over ads that are customized based on their online behavior across different websites. To make choices about interest-based ads from participating third parties, please visit the DAA consumer opt out page. 

**III. Information Use**

Ultrareach may use information that we collect about you for a variety of business purposes, including: to deliver Services that you have requested and enhance your experience on our Site; to perform business analyses or for other purposes to improve the quality of our business, the Site, and the products and services we offer; or in accordance with your consent.

**IV. Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We take very seriously our responsibility to maintain your privacy with respect to your information. We will therefore share that information only with the following entities, and only under these circumstances: with entities that provide services on our behalf, including Site development, maintenance and support, only to the extent that these entities need the information to perform their services or as required by law, unless any additional use or sharing of the information is separately permitted under another provision of this Privacy Policy; with identified entities whose products or services you specifically use or request to receive while you use the Site; when we believe that doing so is required by law, may be necessary to protect any person’s property, rights, or safety, or to investigate a potential violation of law, will help to enforce any terms of use or other legal agreement, or will help resolve disputes that arise in the ordinary course of business, or in the event of a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale; in aggregated or other non-personally identifiable form; or in accordance with your consent.

**V. Third Party Sites**

If you click on or interact with a hyperlink or advertisement that you find on the Site, you may leave our Site or send information to a different website. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to your interactions with other websites, even if you find a link to them on our Site, and so you should read the privacy policy of the third-party website provider to see how your personally identifiable information will be treated on its site. 

**VI. Information Security**

The security and confidentiality of your information is extremely important to us, and we take a number of steps to safeguard any personally identifiable information that you provide to us. We use data encryption technology to help protect against loss, misuse or alteration of your information. However, no method of transmitting or storing electronic data is ever completely secure, and therefore we cannot warrant or guarantee that such information will never be accessed, used or released in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy.

**VII. Personally Identifiable Information Contained in User Content**

Some sections of our Site may allow users to post or transmit messages, comments, screen names, computer files and other materials. If you choose to make personally identifiable information public through these Services, Ultrareach will consider that information public and will not limit its disclosure in the manner described here. 

**VIII. Changes in this Privacy Policy**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the most recent version of the Policy on the Site, along with an indication of the date on which the Policy was amended most recently. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of personally identifiable information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. 

**XI. Contact Us**

If you have questions or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, please email info9@ultrasurf.us.

This policy was last updated July 25, 2012
